35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship, circa 1970s; 10 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Road, golf course, and trees in autumn], 17
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Trees on golf course speckled with yellow], 18
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 19
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Road, golf course, and trees in autumn], 20
  - Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship, circa 1970s; 11 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 1
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: House on golf course during the winter], 2
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course during the winter], 3
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Looking out window at a red bush], 4
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Indoor pool], 5
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 6
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Person walking down snowy hill], 7
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: People playing golf on golf course], 8
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Indoor pool], 9
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Cherry tree], 10
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 11
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Aerial view of hosue on golf course], 12
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 13
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 14
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas on golf cart with his dog], 15
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Back view of hosue on golf course], 16
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Side view of hosue on golf course], 17
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Driveway leading up to hosue on golf course], 18
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Aerial view of back of house on golf course], 19
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Backyard of house on golf course, garden], 20
  - Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship, circa 1970s; 12 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 1
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Aerial view of golf course, lake], 2
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Driveway leading up to a house on a golf course], 3
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 4
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 5
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 6
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 7
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Back of a house on a golf course], 8
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lake], 9
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 10
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 11
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 12
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 13
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 14
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 15
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lake and golf course], 16
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Roads running by entrance to golf course], 17
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: House on golf course], 18
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 19
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: House on golf course], 20
  - Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship, circa 1970s; 13 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: People eating outside on patio], 1
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: People eating outside on patio], 2
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 3
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View from a plane over and ocean], 4
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lake], 5
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas sitting on patio], 6
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: People sitting out on patio], 7
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Road running by entrance to golf course], 8
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Toronto airport], 9
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View of city from airplane], 10
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View of city from airplane], 11
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View of city from airplane], 12
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Top of a cruise ship], 13
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Jacket that reas on the back of it "MV Lowell Thomas Discoverer"], 14
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Hallway of cruise ship], 15
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Cruise ship anchored], 16
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: A golden sign in a foreign language], 17
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Carpet of cruise ship], 18
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Top of cruise ship], 19
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Cruise ship anchored], 20
  - Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship, circa 1970s; 14 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Tour boat on water], 1
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas standing next to another man], 2
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas sitting on a red couch], 3
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas on cruise ship], 4
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas standing next to a man with a microphone on cruise ship], 5
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Captain of the ship talking into microphone in front of Lowell Thomas], 6
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Anchored boats], 7
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas on cruise ship], 8
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Man smiling at the top of the cruise ship], 9
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Boat on water], 10
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: A room inside the cruise ship], 11
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas on cruise ship], 12
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Hallway inside cruise ship], 13
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Canadian Coach bus], 14
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View from top of cruise ship], 15
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas eating on cruise ship], 16
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View from top of cruise ship], 17
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View from top of cruise ship], 18
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Window view from cruise ship], 19
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Sign that reads "High Tide Bar"], 20
  - Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship, circa 1970s; 15 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Boat on water], 1
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Top of cruise ship], 2
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Man standing by door on cruise ship], 3
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View from boat], 4
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: People looking out windows (dark picture)], 5
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Edge of cruise ship], 6
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Golf course], 7
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Edge of cruise ship], 8
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View from cruise ship], 9
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Woman at the railing in cruise ship], 10
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View from cruise ship], 11
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas looking out from cruise ship], 12
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Captain speaking into microphone in front of Lowell Thomas], 13
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas and another man at golf course], 14
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Lowell Thomas with a woman in red golf cart, man standing next to them], 15
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View of garden on golf course], 16
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Man riding in red golf cart], 17
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: View of city from airplane], 18
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: On a cruise ship, jacuzzi], 19
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship]: Sign that reads "Midwest Cruises, Inc. MV Lowell Thomas Discoverer"], 20
  - Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship] [Items 1-13] Carousel number 8 [Items 14-20], circa 1970s; 16 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Two men sitting outside], 1
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Older woman sitting outside], 2
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Two women sitting outside], 3
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Lowell Thomas with man and woman on a boat], 4
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Lowell Thomas golfing], 5
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Two women eating at picnic table], 6
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Man and woman eating at picnic table], 7
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Trees in Autumn on gofl course], 8
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: View of Vancouver], 9
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Sign, "Midwest Cruises Inc., MV Lowell Thomas Discoverer"], 10
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Pine trees covered in snow golf course (?)], 11
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Creek in winter], 12
    - [Carousel number 7 [golf; Hammersley Hill Estate; Toronto featuring the M.V. Lowell Thomas Discoverer cruise ship: Flowers in a vase], 13
    - Beginning of Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing] [: Flowers in a vase], 14
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Flowers in a vase], 15
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Flowers in a vase], 16
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Flowers in a vase], 17
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Little boy sitting on "Santa's" lap], 18
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Toronto airport], 19
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Flowers in a vase], 20
  - Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing], circa 1971, circa 1970s; 17 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Many items laid out on table], 1
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Restaurant], 2
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Women standing around table piled with items], 3
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Table decorated for Christmas], 4
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Table decorated for Christmas, items for sale], 5
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Man taking a picture with "Santa"], 6
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Woman smiling], 7
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Tables decorated for Christmas, items for sale], 8
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Woman with "Santa"], 9
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Woman with "Santa"], 10
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Table set up with Christmas items], 11